Valencia Walker



valenciawalker37@yahoo.com



8103482944



linkedin.com/in/valencia-walker-306a7477

Summary

Greetings, Hiring Manager,

I am Valencia Walker, a Master of Psychology Grad student at the University of Phoenix. My two Undergraduate background is in The Field of Health Administration.

I obtained my B.S. in Health Administration from the University of Michigan-Flint in 2018. I received my A.S. in Health Administration in 2013 from Colorado Technical University.

I've previously worked as Medicare Advocate as an Independent Contractor; I have former experience as a Research Clinical Coordinator. I have experience as a certified Medicare Advocate. (810) I'm pursuing my Master of Psychology and a Software Engineering Certificate from Coding Temple. My email:

ValenciaWalker37@yahoo.com.valenciw90@email.phoenix.edu.

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/ in/valencia-walker-306a7477/

Thank you

Valencia Walker

ValenciaWalker37@yahoo.com.

valenciw90@email.phoenix.edu.https://www.linkedin.com/in/valencia-walker-306a7477/

(810) 348 2944

(810) 280-3784

(810) 297-0398

Experience



Volunteer

Hurley Medical Center

Sep 2012 - Aug 2014 (2 years)

Assisting medical personnel . organizing medical supplies , feeding patients, assisting patients .

Student Intern

Hurley Medical Center

Sep 2012 - Present (10 years 8 months)

Assisting medical personnel . organizing medical supplies , feeding patients, assisting patients .

Medicare Advocate

AgentC Solutions

Oct 2022 - Present (7 months)

independent contractors. A successful advocate will possess the desire to help others optimize and understand their benefits. Patience, empathy, and effective solid communication skills are imperative to success. Must be comfortable working from home and enjoy a modern gig experience. The Medicare Advocate will be part of a fast-paced environment, so he or she must be capable of working independently and handling a wide variety of situations to qualify individuals over the phone and transfer them to licensed insurance agents.

Responsibilities:

Login to be connected with a high volume of people eligible to optimize their enrollment in Medicare Desire to help folks understand something they know little about Discipline to stay consistent with a process that is always successful when followed Ability to work through challenges to experience success



🦅 Grad Student MS General Psychology

University of Phoenix Jan 2022 - Present (1 year 4 months) MS General Psychology

Data Research Specialist

PACE Group International

Nov 2020 - Jan 2022 (1 year 3 months)

Research, Data mining gathering data for the aviation industry, focused on partnering and developing successful business relationships with suppliers and customers, producing research data with a dedication in providing our colleagues with their aircraft parts and engine needs all around the world. #Aviation #Aerospace #Datamining https://pacegroupinternational.com



Clinical Research Coordinator

AAMRC Medical Research Center

Oct 2019 - Nov 2019 (2 months)

The Clinical Research Coordinator (CRC) is a specialized working with and under the direction of the clinical Principal Investigator (PI). While the Principal Investigator is primarily responsible for the overall design, conduct, and management of the clinical trial, the CRC supports, facilitates, and coordinates the daily clinical trial activities and plays a critical role in the conduct of the study. By performing these duties, the CRC works with the PI, department, sponsor, and guide the administration of the compliance,

Valencia Walker - page 1

financial, personnel, and other related aspects of the clinical study Working with and under the direction of the Clinical Principal Investigator Working with staff members assisting with varied clinical research studies such as fatty liver studies, asthma studies, triglyceride studies, diabetes studies.

Confidentiality Agreement for Survey Coordinator



Confidentiality Agreement for Survey Coordinator

University of Chicago

Sep 2019 - Sep 2019 (1 month)

Independent Contractor. Collect while storing research data of study participants surrounding the Flint Water Crisis of Attitudes And Behaviors, In Flint After The Water Crisis: A Human Rights-Informed Community-Based Research Project gathering data.

Intern

Wellness AIDS Services, Inc.

Aug 2017 - Dec 2017 (5 months)

Filing Document's, Creating Medical Needle kits, Creating Sex Safety kits. Organizing Medical Supplies. Administrative clerical tasks forming calendars and brochures organizing CTR Risk Assessment Med Documents.

Food Preperation

Sadexco Magic

Mar 2017 - Aug 2017 (6 months)

Reading recipes and or/product instructions. using knowledge of temperature necessities and spoilage. using regulatory rules and necessary procedures. General cooking responsibilities. complies with HACCP

procedures and policies. Cleaning workstations and taking temperature.

Office Assistant

University of Michigan-Flint

Aug 2014 - Sep 2014 (2 months)

Flint, organizing while maintaining the establishment/answering phones and responding knowledgeably to all inquiries of the Student Success Center.

Education

Co

Coding Temple

Certificate, Software Engineering

2023 - 2023

Software Engineering

April 2023-June 2023

Coding Temple Bootcamp

Certificate Ten-week program.

Java

HTML / CSS+++

Python

Databases

Flask

FLINT

University of Michigan-Flint

Bachelor's Degree, Bachelors in Health Administration 2014 - Apr 2018

Colorado Technical University

Health Administration Associates in Science Service, Health/Health Care Administration/Management 2011 - 2013

Health Administration A.S.

Licenses & Certifications



HIPAA - Advanced HIPAA Training



Medicare Advocate - Agency C soultions LLC

Skills

Life Insurance • Event Planning • Microsoft Word • Microsoft Excel • research skills • Social Media • business management skills • Microsoft Office • PowerPoint • Organization Skills